You can’t hide from an evil that lives within.
The Inhabitant is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Jerren Lauder.
Like any other teenage girl, Tara is just surviving high school —
yet her father and mother seem strangely distant.
Amidst a nearby spree of gruesome ax murders, Tara has sightings of terrifying
entities, forcing her to question her own sanity and shocking ancestry.
Tara, played by Odessa A'zion.
Emily, played by Leslie Bibb.
Ben, played by Dermot Mulroney.
Suzy Beemer, played by Lizze Broadway.
Carl, played by Michael Cooper Jr..
Aunt Diane, played by Mary Buss.
The Inhabitant is a 2022 American horror-thriller film directed by Jerren Lauder, written by Kevin
Bachar and starring Odessa A'zion, Leslie Bibb, Dermot Mulroney, and Lizze Broadway.
The Inhabitant follows a teenage girl who fears that she may be behind a series of gruesome
murders in her town, particularly as she is a descendant of Lizzie Borden.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.